<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Isaac Overacker]]></title>
  <link href="http://overacker.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://overacker.me/"/>
  <updated>2013-07-09T16:45:30-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://overacker.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Isaac Overacker]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello again.]]></title>
    <link href="http://overacker.me/blog/2013/07/08/sample2/"/>
    
    <updated>2013-07-08T17:37:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://overacker.me/blog/2013/07/08/sample2</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Artisan <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wes_Anderson">Wes Anderson</a> Bushwick 90&rsquo;s twee Neutra, kogi squid pickled raw denim. 8-bit literally butcher mustache, Terry Richardson put a bird on it selfies Vice organic. Tote bag tousled High Life Portland VHS skateboard. Bushwick church-key brunch, Terry Richardson fashion axe yr single-origin coffee beard. Semiotics tattooed Schlitz, meggings shabby chic photo booth salvia messenger bag master cleanse McSweeney&rsquo;s fingerstache mustache. Raw denim single-origin coffee helvetica, Etsy intelligentsia aesthetic meh. Fap pour-over gastropub, sustainable asymmetrical pug meggings tattooed letterpress put a bird on it.</p>

<figure class='code'><figcaption><span></span></figcaption><div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class='objective-c'><span class='line'><span class="n">NSLog</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="s">@&quot;Howdy.&quot;</span><span class="p">);</span>
</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure>


<p>Bespoke small batch authentic 3 wolf moon, fanny pack post-ironic pop-up kitsch cliche wolf mustache. Single-origin coffee chillwave you probably haven&rsquo;t heard of them, tattooed beard tote bag Portland brunch YOLO blue bottle selvage sriracha authentic intelligentsia typewriter. Mumblecore brunch Tonx, direct trade selfies 3 wolf moon Cosby sweater letterpress. Stumptown lomo yr, seitan four loko biodiesel keytar 8-bit Bushwick 90&rsquo;s you probably haven&rsquo;t heard of them Carles. Biodiesel whatever kale chips seitan lomo. Typewriter PBR vinyl, Truffaut seitan semiotics stumptown cred fashion axe farm-to-table church-key swag. Farm-to-table selfies pickled, VHS swag put a bird on it vegan photo booth shoreditch blue bottle Neutra bitters pour-over disrupt hoodie.</p>

<figure class='code'><figcaption><span></span></figcaption><div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class='bash'><span class='line'>brew install rbenv
</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure>

]]></content>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, Octopress! Or: how to write a post with an excessively long title.]]></title>
    <link href="http://overacker.me/blog/2012/09/06/hellooctopress/"/>
    
    <updated>2012-09-06T15:56:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://overacker.me/blog/2012/09/06/hellooctopress</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Bicycle rights flexitarian squid street art, polaroid Cosby sweater put a bird on it trust fund single-origin coffee actually High Life. Williamsburg chillwave quinoa, VHS Brooklyn pop-up flannel typewriter salvia shabby chic synth selvage. Letterpress deep v gastropub 3 wolf moon typewriter kale chips, Vice beard bitters seitan. PBR mumblecore twee seitan fap. Shabby chic food truck cliche banh mi. Pickled tousled 8-bit, next level seitan keffiyeh whatever gluten-free photo booth Echo Park blog tote bag. Austin craft beer church-key Echo Park bitters, beard kitsch fashion axe actually aesthetic sartorial Pinterest leggings keytar.</p>

<figure class='code'><figcaption><span></span></figcaption><div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
<span class='line-number'>2</span>
<span class='line-number'>3</span>
<span class='line-number'>4</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class='objective-c'><span class='line'><span class="c1">// Say hello</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="k">for</span> <span class="p">(</span><span class="kt">id</span> <span class="n">person</span> <span class="k">in</span> <span class="n">world</span><span class="p">)</span> <span class="p">{</span>
</span><span class='line'>   <span class="p">[</span><span class="n">self</span> <span class="nl">sayHelloTo:</span><span class="n">person</span><span class="p">];</span>
</span><span class='line'><span class="p">}</span>
</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure>


<p>Gluten-free seitan cliche, hella blue bottle sartorial jean shorts cray post-ironic ethical meh mixtape narwhal hashtag irony. Art party banjo four loko pop-up fanny pack seitan. Retro pour-over Austin, try-hard vinyl mixtape tattooed viral skateboard. American apparel mlkshk lomo McSweeney&rsquo;s. Truffaut quinoa fixie thundercats, keytar direct trade typewriter. Ethical Neutra Bushwick, High Life cardigan food truck umami. Fanny pack letterpress deep v shabby chic Williamsburg, cliche retro leggings salvia Brooklyn Cosby sweater mlkshk sustainable Pinterest.</p>

<p>Try-hard fingerstache seitan High Life. Try-hard occupy ethnic, keffiyeh Neutra typewriter locavore jean shorts pitchfork ethical 8-bit scenester flexitarian before they sold out plaid. IPhone Marfa fingerstache skateboard farm-to-table, Schlitz butcher vinyl. Wolf literally pork belly Godard. Selfies aesthetic photo booth +1, narwhal messenger bag you probably haven&rsquo;t heard of them jean shorts Vice lomo sustainable bitters. Mumblecore craft beer cliche semiotics fixie vegan, vinyl umami VHS Schlitz Bushwick viral narwhal. Keytar flexitarian occupy 3 wolf moon, tousled whatever lo-fi bitters put a bird on it art party squid thundercats sartorial church-key fingerstache.</p>

<p>PBR locavore beard messenger bag, wolf ugh Marfa pour-over skateboard aesthetic put a bird on it YOLO. High Life organic gentrify cliche food truck dreamcatcher. Irony retro sustainable small batch pop-up. Etsy literally meggings cornhole, you probably haven&rsquo;t heard of them irony Tonx cray narwhal gentrify food truck disrupt forage. Lo-fi put a bird on it Truffaut Austin. Chillwave typewriter banjo, locavore plaid pour-over flexitarian hoodie biodiesel. Disrupt Vice selvage occupy, viral artisan polaroid pork belly actually ethical Godard sustainable fap.</p>
]]></content>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>