<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: linker-errors | Isaac Overacker]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.overacker.me/blog/categories/linker-errors/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.overacker.me/"/>
  <updated>2015-01-25T16:59:09-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.overacker.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Isaac Overacker]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Architecture Headaches with CocoaPods]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.overacker.me/blog/2014/08/03/architecture-headaches-with-cocoapods/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-03T18:22:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.overacker.me/blog/2014/08/03/architecture-headaches-with-cocoapods</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I recently inherited an iOS project from another developer.  This project was not using CocoaPods for dependency management, so naturally, I converted it to using CocoaPods as soon as I could.  When I first installed the pods, I received this warning in the console:</p>

<p><div class='bogus-wrapper'><notextile><figure class='code'><figcaption><span>Terminal </span></figcaption>
<div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
<span class='line-number'>2</span>
<span class='line-number'>3</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class=''><span class='line'>[!] Found multiple values (&lt;code>armv7&lt;/code>, &lt;code>armv7s&lt;/code>) for the
</span><span class='line'>architectures (&lt;code>ARCHS&lt;/code>) build setting for the &lt;code>Pods&lt;/code>
</span><span class='line'>target definition. Using the first.</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure></notextile></div></p>

<p>It seemed harmless enough, and the project built without problems for the iPhone simulator.  I carried on for a few weeks working on new features, and then I tried to build a version of the app targeting the iOS devices.  Suddenly, I had linker errors.</p>

<p><div class='bogus-wrapper'><notextile><figure class='code'><div class="highlight"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre class="line-numbers"><span class='line-number'>1</span>
<span class='line-number'>2</span>
<span class='line-number'>3</span>
<span class='line-number'>4</span>
</pre></td><td class='code'><pre><code class=''><span class='line'>&ldquo;&lt;em>OBJC_CLASS&lt;/em>$_FBSession&rdquo;, referenced from:
</span><span class='line'>  objc-class-ref in MySourceFile.m
</span><span class='line'>  &hellip;
</span><span class='line'>ld: symbol(s) not found for architecture armv7s</span></code></pre></td></tr></table></div></figure></notextile></div></p>

<p>I looked around for solutions, but of course with linker errors it&rsquo;s can be very difficult to find answers for a particular issue.  Finally, after many hours of searching, reading, and highly scientific trial and error, I decided to look into the multiple architecture warning from CocoaPods, and that&rsquo;s where I found my issue.  In this particular case, the Pods-* targets in my Pods project were targeting armv7 (which is pretty obvious from the CocoaPods warning, but a few weeks had passed), whereas my main app target architectures included both armv7 and armv7s, hence the linker error above.</p>

<p>The solution was to update the target architectures for the app to <code>$(ARCHS_STANDARD_32_BIT)</code> instead of manually specifying both <code>armv7</code> and <code>armv7s</code>.  Then, when running <code>pod install</code>, the <code>$(ARCHS_STANDARD_32_BIT)</code> is set for the Pods-* projects as well and everything is happy.</p>

<p><em>Note: the reason armv7 and armv7s architectures had been specified for the app is that there is a dependency on a library that does not yet support 64-bit architectures.  It looks like <code>$(ARCHS_STANDARD_32_BIT)</code> is a much better way to handle that situation.</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
